Die Young
活不长
歌手：Ke$ha
压制:随Feng
I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums
我听到你心跳得和鼓点一样
Oh what a shame that you came here with someone
太丢人了吧你还带个人来
So while you're here in my arms
就在我抱着你的时候
Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young
让我们享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长
We're gonna die young, we're gonna die young
我们根本活不长 我们根本活不长
Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young
让我们享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长
Hearts, out of minds
年轻的心们 疯了
Running till we out of time
狂奔的时间 没了
Wild childs, looking good
野孩子们 长得漂亮
Living hard, just like we should
野蛮生存 本该这样
Don't care who's watching when we tearing up
管他谁在看 我们会自顾自哭地狂浪
You know
你懂的
That magic that we got that nobody can touch
我们之间的魔力他们永远不明白
You show
只有你懂的
Looking for some trouble tonight
今晚咱来点刺激的
Take my hand, I'll show you the wild side
抓住我的手 让你看看姐狂野的一面
Like it's the last night of our lives
疯得就像明儿就要死了
We'll keep dancing 'till we die
死之前继续狂舞
I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums
我听到你心跳得像鼓点一样
Oh what a shame that you came here with someone
太丢人了吧你还带个人来
So while you're here in my arms
就在我抱着你的时候
Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young
就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长
We're gonna die young, we're gonna die young
我们根本活不长 我们根本活不长
Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young
就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长
Punks, taking shots
小青年 酒杯都倒过来
Stripping down to dirty socks
妹纸们 丝袜都丢上来
Music up, getting hot
DJ们 音乐都嗨起来
Kiss me, give you all you got
亲吻我 本事都使出来
It's pretty obvious that you got a crush
你浑身上下都写着你想要
You know
你懂的
That magic in your pants is making blush
你牛仔裤里的魔棒让我热血上涌
You show
给姐瞧瞧
Looking for some trouble tonight
今晚咱来点刺激的
Take my hand, I'll show you the wild side
抓住我的手 让你看看姐狂野的一面
Like it's the last night of our lives
疯得就像明儿就要死
We'll keep dancing 'till we die
死之前继续狂舞
I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums
我听到你心跳得和鼓点一样
Oh what a shame that you came here with someone
太丢人了吧你还带个人来
So while you're here in my arms
就在我抱着你的时候
Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young
就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长
I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums
我听到你心跳得和鼓点一样
Oh what a shame that you came here with someone
太丢人了吧你还带个人来
So while you're here in my arms
就在我抱着你的时候
Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young
就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长
We're gonna die young, we're gonna die young
我们根本活不长 我们根本活不长
Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young
就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长
压制:随Feng